what's up everybody this is episode one
of the booty chronicles item Bret
contras aka the glue guy this is my
friend Hattie boydle and and today we
are giving a seminar build your best
booty seminar here at Santa Monica this
is gonna suffice for an intro for now
[Music]
[Applause]
so we just got into Santa Monica right
right and Patty we're doing a seminar
tomorrow killed your best booty seminar
and so tonight we're lifting weights I'm
out of breath as I'm trying to hang with
Hattie deadlifting here but tonight we
got to put together the goody bags and
then tomorrow it's on
[Applause]
he knows
[Music]
[Applause]
50 trustus fungus from China we can't
even sell them because this rubs off so
I'm giving them all away
words because there's Hitler
sister hiccups
these are things okay so before this
blue section in the gym all these
machines so she saw that interview and I
had just the enjoins to Ivy oMG did all
these girls like I used to
two hours so I want you guys to do
sideline introductions
I want you in the frontal plane don't be
flexible in the particularly and what
you freeways going to draw externally
rotated which will feel more in the
Walker one
and then internally rotated once it took
down and this is what you will end up
like eating the most events so if you
all three of them
now when you point the toe up you will
not feel much glue
this one booth to be don't we start in
the air
so keep your hands up keep your hands up
I said well how many of you think you're
symmetrical raise your hand so don't
wait a weird ones
my point is it's normal why would you
not happy with this stronger than the
other you spend your whole life going
boom kicking so this this skipping steps
are your left and then you break hip
flexors up more think about it it makes
sense to be like get good like an
athlete I need a switch so we need to
get our heads and that's weird to have
one side that's trying to do a baby's
probably should be but you would want to
it should normalize a little bit over
time okay we're driving to lunch
we got Lizzy
- pull tight because they cross the
sacrum when the glutes contract 71% of
the force of the glutes transfer
directly across that SI joint pulling it
tight and that's called formed side
force closure so we like locked out legs
so I think with the loop that loot bag
you're going to have to put it around
others below your knees or above your
knees depending on how poor your
strength under that you can also this is
when you've got like a an elastic band
you put it around your mid foot like
these going to be two times around the
mid foot of the ankles must be like
above the knees sometimes people like
balloons
[Music]
like 90 but then one of
automatic for her
it came and then when it comes up to
that technique techniques and getting
stronger
she not coming
the top you're just going to jack up
your traps it's ugly you know but she
got some amazing exercise
they dug deeper into accounting
eighteen deeper nineteen
20 little deeper
that we want now way to see what you're
doing it without me you've curled you
hinge back and I want you to sing
doublet though okay
what's your name Alex you're tucking the
whole way I don't want you tucking here
and want you tucking at the top so then
come down there but don't slide on the
pitch you learn
[Music]
driving up
four five six seven eight you went over
squat squat variations we want over
deadlifts I had the hiccups all day we
went over hip thrust we had so many
types of interests that we taught so I
want to thank all the people who came to
this seminar you guys are awesome are
they Hattie for being my co-host thanks
Bret being my co-host yes we make a good
team thank you guys for watching I will
[Music]